-Hey. -Hey.
-嘿 -嘿
I saw the Porsche parked out front.
我看到保時捷停在前門
Can I get the keys? I'll take that bad boy for a spin.
你能把鑰匙借給我一下嗎？ 我想帶那個壞男孩去兜個風
Ross drives it? When I ask, you say you're the only one allowed to.
羅斯可以開它？我問你時 你說只有你能開它
He's my brother, plus he drives so slow he couldn't hurt it.
他是我哥哥，而且他開車 跟烏龜一樣，不會出事的
It's a car, Monica, not a rocket ship.
它是輛車子，摩妮卡，不是火箭
Just replace the bulbs in the brake lights after you're done.
兜完風後，幫我換一下剎車燈的燈泡
-Hey. -Hi.
-嘿 -嗨
Saw the Porsche. Looking good. When can I take it out again?
我看到保時捷了，它真的很酷 我什麼時候能再開著它去兜風？
-You let Joey drive it? -I've never driven it. Not once.
-你讓喬伊開保時捷？ -我從來沒開過它，一次都沒有
Okay, once. Okay, I drive it all the time.
好吧，只有一次 好吧，我常開著它出門
So much for the "you-can-drive-it but-don't-tell-Rachel" plan.
我們的「你可以開它去兜風 但別告訴瑞秋」計劃宣告失敗
Wow, I can't believe you lied to me.
哇，我不敢相信你騙我
I can fix this. Monica, Rachel thinks all you talk about is the wedding.
交給我來吧，摩妮卡 瑞秋認為你只會談婚禮的事
I won't let you drive the Porsche because you're a terrible driver.
我不會讓你開保時捷 因為你是個很差勁的駕駛
There. That wasn't about the wedding.
好了，那跟婚禮的事無關
If you want a ride in the Porsche, I'll take you around the block.
如果你想開保時捷去兜風 我可以載你在街角轉一下
You got a couple hours?
你接下來幾小時都沒事嗎？
The One With Chandler's Dad
本集播出：錢德的父親
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Whew, that was a brisk ride.
喔，那真的痛快
-Take the top down, did you? -Only way to fly.
-你開了篷吧？ -這樣開跟飛上天差不多
Give me the keys. Monica's wrong. I'm an excellent driver.
把鑰匙給我，摩妮卡錯了 我是個很棒的駕駛
You're fast and irresponsible. That adds up to a bad driver.
你開車飛快，又不負責任 你的確是個差勁的駕駛
In high school, that added up to head cheerleader.
高中時那些特點 讓我成為啦啦隊長
Did you see how she looked at me?
你看到那個女孩看我的眼神了嗎？
She must've seen me cruising in the bad boy.
她一定看到了我開保時捷的模樣
-She's checking out your beehive. -What?
-她在看你的鳥窩頭 -什麼？
-Give me a brush. -The keys.
-把梳子給我 -鑰匙給我
-No way! -Well, no brush.
-不行 -那我就不給你梳子
Fine. It doesn't matter.
好吧，那不重要
If I remember correctly, there's a comb on the floor of the bathroom.
如果我沒記錯 洗手間地上有一把梳子
Alimony.
這是我的贍養費
We still haven't gotten an RSVP from your dad.
你爸還沒寄回函給我們
Oh, right. Maybe that's because I didn't send him an invitation.
喔，對，或許那是因為 我沒寄喜帖給他
He's your father. He should be at our wedding.
他是你爸爸，他應該來 參加我們的婚禮
I don't even know him. I haven't seen him in years.
我甚至不認得他 我好幾年沒跟他見過面
And when he finds out he wasn't asked?
如果他知道我們沒有邀請他呢？
We don't run in the same circles.
我們的生活圈不一樣
I hang out with you guys and he...
我跟你們來往，而他…
stars in a drag show in Vegas.
他在拉斯維加斯表演變裝秀
I think I want to trade circles.
我想和他交換生活圈
You don't want him there. Nobody will stare at the bride...
你不會想邀請他來的 沒有人會看著新娘…
when the groom's father's wearing a backless dress.
因為新郎的爸爸穿著露背洋裝
As long as he's not wearing a white dress and veil, I don't care.
那又怎麼樣？只要他不穿婚紗 我根本不會在乎的
I think I need to do some shopping.
我想我得去買點東西
Nice.
太棒了
My God!
我的天啊！
-What do you think you're doing? -Just washing the windshield.
-你以為你在做什麼？ -我只是在洗擋風玻璃
There's no way I'll let you drive this car.
我絕不會讓你開這輛車
Just hand over the keys.
你為什麼不把鑰匙還給我？
Oh!
喔！
Do not start this car.
別啟動引擎
Okay, okay. I will give you 20 bucks...
好吧，我給你二十塊…
if you get out of this car right now. Hey!
只要你立刻下車，嘿！
Look.
聽著
If you're so freaked out, get in the car.
如果你真的那麼害怕，快上車吧
With you? Yeah, right.
跟你一起去兜風？對，是啊
All right.
好吧
Okay, okay, okay.
好吧…
-What are you doing? Get in front. -In the death seat?!
-你在做什麼？坐到前面來 -你要我坐死亡座椅？
-Hey, guys. -Hi, sweetie.
-嘿，大家好 -嗨，甜心
-Ready to go? -My purse is at Mon's. I'll be back.
-準備要走了嗎？ -我的皮包在摩妮卡家，我馬上回來
-Wait a minute. -What? Oh.
-等一下 -什麼？喔
That one kept going.
我還在頭暈
So, you and Phoebe, huh?
你跟菲比在交往？
-How long have you been going out? -A month.
-你們交往多久了？ -一個多月
We ought to get to know each other better.
我們應該多多瞭解彼此
-Sure. I'd like that. -Yeah. So, uh...
-當然，我很願意 -對，所以…
What's your name?
你叫什麼名字？
-It's Jake. -Joey.
-我是傑克 -我是喬伊
-Do you like the Knicks? -Yeah, big fan.
-你喜歡尼克隊嗎？ -當然，我是他們的頭號球迷
Me too. There's a game Tuesday. Do you want to go?
我也是，星期二有比賽 你要一起去嗎？
Great! Let me make sure I'm not doing anything Tuesday.
太棒了，我得先確定星期二我沒事
Here.
拿去吧
-What's this? -Your suitcase. We're going to Vegas.
-這是什麼？ -你的行李，我們要去拉斯維加斯
Are you serious? Eloping? No more stupid wedding stuff.
你是認真的嗎？我們要私奔？ 不必再籌備那個笨婚禮
No more these flowers, these flowers. Think of the money we'll save.
不必再煩惱那些花 想想我們省了多少錢
We're not eloping. Can our wedding be bigger, please?
我們沒有要私奔，我喜歡花 我們的婚禮能再盛大一點嗎？拜託
We're going to see your dad.
我們要去找你爸
I want to get to know my father-in-law.
我想認識我公公
When we went over this, I won.
我們已經談過這件事，我贏了
No, you didn't. Honey, just so you know...
不，你沒贏，甜心，你應該知道…
Now that you're marrying me, you don't get to win anymore.
現在你要娶我，你是贏不了的
Forget it. I don't want to go. I don't want to see him.
算了吧，我不想去，我不想見到他
I know your dad embarrassed you.
我知道你爸讓你覺得丟臉
All kids are embarrassed by their parents.
所有的孩子 都會覺得自己的父母很丟臉
You need a new word for what I went through.
你得想個新說法來形容我的經歷
In high school, he came to all my swim meets...
在高中的時候 他參加了我所有的游泳比賽…
dressed as a Hollywood starlet.
每次都打扮成不一樣的好萊塢明星
Hard enough to be 14, skinny, wearing Speedos Mom promised I'd grow into.
我十四歲時日子很不好過 瘦巴巴的，穿著太大的泳褲 我媽還說有一天它會適合我
You look up in the stands. There's your dad cheering you on.
我抬頭看著看台 發現我爸在為我加油
Dressed as Carmen Miranda, wearing a headdress with real fruit...
他打扮成卡曼米蘭達 戴著有真水果頭飾的帽子…
that he'll later give to your friends as a healthy snack.
之後他會把那些水果 交給你的朋友，作為飯後果
He was at every one of your swim meets cheering you on.
重點是他參加了 你每一場游泳比賽，幫你加油
That's a pretty great dad.
他是個好爸爸
He had sex with Mr. Garibaldi.
他跟嘉利巴迪先生上床
-Who's Mr. Garibaldi? -Does it matter?!
-誰是嘉利巴迪先生？ -那很重要嗎？！
You're not 14 anymore, okay? Maybe it's time you let that stuff go.
你不再是十四歲的孩子，好嗎？ 或許你該忘了那些事
If he's not at your wedding, you'll regret it for the rest of your life.
如果他沒來參加你的婚禮 你會遺憾終生的
Okay, but I'm just doing this for you.
好吧，但我這麼做是為了你
-I never get to win anymore? -How much did you ever win before?
-我永遠都贏不了嗎？ -你以前又贏過幾次了？
You know how when you're wearing pants and you lean forward...
你知道當你穿著褲子 身體往前傾時…
I check out your underwear?
我可以看到你的內褲嗎？
Well, when Jake did it...
喔，當傑克那麼做時…
I saw that he was wearing women's underwear.
我看到他穿著女人的內褲
I know. They were mine.
我知道，那是我的內褲
Oh!
喔！
No, no, wait. That's weird.
不，等一下，那太奇怪了
We were goofing around, and I dared him to try them on.
我們只是鬧著玩 我跟他打賭他不敢穿上它們
That's weird!
那真的很奇怪
-I'm wearing his briefs right now. -That's kind of hot.
-我正穿著他的內褲 -那真的很性感
I think so too. And that little flap? Great for holding my lipstick.
我也那麼認為，你知道那個小洞嗎？ 它剛好可以拿來放我的口紅
I wouldn't know about that.
我倒是不知道那一點
Jake says that women's underwear is actually more comfortable.
傑克說，事實上女人的內褲更舒服
He loves how silk feels against his skin.
他喜歡絲質內褲貼在他皮膚上的感覺
Next he'll say your high heels are good for his posture.
接下來他會說 穿上你的高跟鞋他更婀娜多姿
There's nothing wrong with Jake. He is all man.
傑克沒有什麼不正常的 他是個貨真價實的男人
I think more than you.
我擔心的是你
He looked like a real lumberjack in those pink lacies.
那看起來像是 穿著粉紅色蕾絲內褲的伐木工人
Only a man completely secure in his masculinity could...
我是說只有真正 相信自己男子氣概的男人…
walk around in women's underwear. I don't think you could.
才會穿上女人的內褲 我敢說你辦不到
-I am secure with my masculinity. -Okay, whatever.
-我很相信我的男子氣概 -好吧，隨便你
You've seen my huge stack of porn.
你看過我收集的色情雜誌了吧？
God, I forgot how much I love driving.
天啊，我都忘了我有多愛開車了
I have got to get my license renewed.
我得去換新駕照
You don't have a valid driver's license? Pull over right now.
你的駕照過期了？馬上停車
You're so tense. You just gotta relax, okay?
羅斯，你太緊張了 你得放輕鬆，好嗎？
Okay? Just need to relax. All right? Just need to relax.
你只需要放輕鬆，好嗎？放輕鬆
What are you..? That's not funny. Stop horsing around.
你在…？那一點都不好笑，別鬧了
I am not horsing around, okay?
我沒有胡鬧，好嗎？
I am "Porsche-ing" around.
我在「開保時捷」兜風
Uh-oh.
喔
Stay calm. Nothing will happen. You're not in that much trouble.
保持冷靜，不會有事的 你沒有惹上大麻煩
Really? You think so?
真的嗎？你那麼認為？
I'm talking to myself. You're going down!
我是在跟自己說話，你死定了！
（四後俱樂部）
Has someone taken your order?
有人來幫你們點東西了嗎？
Oh, yeah. She did. He did. She? I'm sorry, I'm new. I don't...
對，她來過了，是他才對，是她嗎？ 抱歉，我第一次來，我不…
-I just ordered a beer. -You're straight. I get it.
-我點了一杯啤酒 -你是異性戀，我懂了
If we called your dad, we'd have better seats.
如果我們打電話給你爸 就能坐到比較好一點的位置
I don't want him to know we're here yet. I'm not ready.
我不想讓他知道我們來了 我還沒有準備好
He won't be too happy to see me either.
而且他看到我也不會太高興
Why not?
為什麼？
He's kind of tried to contact me...
我不知道我有沒有告訴你…
-a lot the last few years. -What?
-過去幾年來他常常試著跟我聯絡 -什麼？
Yeah. He's made phone calls, written letters.
對，他會打電話，寫信給我
He came to New York. I said I was too busy.
他會到紐約來，但我總是說我很忙
It's very "Cats in the Cradle." I don't want to get into it.
那就像是「惡意缺席」我真的不想談
Here we go.
節目要開始了
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome the incomparable...
各位先生女士，歡迎與世無雙的…
Helena Handbasket.
海蓮娜漢德巴斯奇
Hello, darlings.
嗨，我的小親親們
And there's Daddy.
他就是我爸
Switch places with me. Come on! I'll go under, you go over.
快跟我換位置，快點！ 我在上面，你在下面
-Yeah, I'll get right on that. -Come on!
-對，我願意那麼做 -快點
What? No. Hey, Rach, come on.
-什麼？不，瑞秋，別那樣 -快點
I'm sure we won't get arrested for this.
我相信我們不會因此被逮捕
Hi, officer. Was I going a little too fast?
嗨，警官，我的速度有點快嗎？
Oh, my God.
喔，我的天啊
-Can I see your license, please? -Absolutely.
-麻煩你把駕照拿出來 -沒問題
It's weird. I had a dream last night that I was stopped by a policeman.
這太奇怪了，我昨晚做了一個夢 夢到我被一個警察攔下來
And then he...
然後他…
Well, I probably shouldn't tell you the rest.
或許我不該告訴你接下來的情節
-Your license. -Yes. Here you go, Officer...
-你的駕照 -對，在這裡，警官…
Handsome.
帥哥警官
-It's Hanson. -Oops, sorry. My mistake.
-是韓森才對 -喔，對不起，我看錯了
Dear Lord!
我的天啊！
-Wow! -Here it comes.
-哇！ -好了
This is a great picture.
這張照片很漂亮
Really? You think so? You know, I had just rolled right out of bed.
真的嗎？你真的那麼想？ 拍照時我才剛剛起床
You look phenomenal.
你看起來很美
She should! It was taken 10 years ago!
一點都沒錯，那是十年前的照片了
You know, you probably...
你知道的，或許你很納悶
wonder about the old date.
日期有點不太對勁
Yes. You're an Aquarius, huh?
沒錯，你是水瓶座嗎？
-I'll bet you're a Gemini. -No.
-我敢說你是雙子座 -不是
-Taurus? -No.
-金牛座？ -不是
-Virgo? -No.
-處女座？ -不是
-Sagittarius? -Yep.
-射手座？ -對
I knew it. I knew it!
我就知道
You won't speed anymore, right?
不要再超速了，好嗎？
I won't speed.
我不會超速的
-Promise to take care of this? -I promise.
-你發誓你會去換駕照？ -我發誓
Let him drive. Does he have a license?
還有，讓他開車，他有駕照嗎？
-Can he handle a stick? -Well...
-他會開手動的車嗎？ -喔…
I can handle a stick!
我會開手動的車！
-That can't be your father. -I've been saying that for years.
-他不可能是你爸 -多年來我一直是那麼告訴自己
-Oh, my God! -What?
-喔，我的天啊 -什麼？
That's Mr. Garibaldi playing the piano.
彈鋼琴的人就是嘉利巴迪先生
Hello, and welcome to the show.
嗨，歡迎你們來看表演
I see some of our regulars in the audience.
在觀眾席中我看到一些常客
And a couple of irregulars.
還有一些新面孔
-He's coming into the audience. -Relax. You'll be fine.
-他要走進觀眾席裡了 -放輕鬆，你會沒事的
Oh, much better. You're invisible now.
喔，好多了，現在你成了隱形人
-Where are you from? -Bakersfield.
-你是從哪裡來的？ -貝克斯菲德
-I'm sorry? -Bakersfield.
-對不起？ -貝克斯菲德
No, no, I heard. I'm just sorry.
不，我聽到了，我只是覺得很遺憾
I'll meet you back at the hotel.
我無法接受這種事情 我們回飯店碰面
Look, a standing ovation already. So early in the show.
大家看，已經有人站起來鼓掌 節目才剛剛開始
Turn around, darling. Let me see your pretty face.
轉身吧，親愛的 讓我看看你帥氣的臉
Can we have our drinks, please? Waiter? tress?
我們的飲料能快點送上來嗎？ 服務生？…小姐？
-Hey, Phoebe. -Hey.
-嘿，菲比 -嘿
Check it out.
你看
How much of a man am I?
我很有男子氣概吧？
Wow, nice. Manly, and also kind of a slut.
哇，太棒了，你很有男子氣概 但你也是個蕩婦
I'm beginning to see what Jake was talking about.
我開始瞭解傑克的意思了
The silk feels really good.
絲內褲的感覺真的很舒服
And things aren't as smashed down as I thought they would be.
而那玩意不像我想像中 會擠成一團
That's great.
那真的是太棒了
You have so many more choices than with men's underwear.
而男人的內褲選擇沒那麼多
Bikini, French cut, thong. And the fabrics: cotton, silk, lace.
比基尼，法式剪裁，丁字褲 質料有棉，絲跟蕾絲
You know what I've always wondered about? Pantyhose!
你知道我一直想穿什麼嗎？褲襪！
The way they start at your toe, then they go all the way up to..
從腳趾頭開始一路往上拉到…
-I should go take these off. -I think it's important you do.
-我應該把內褲脫下來的，對吧？ -我想你最好那麼做
What's your name?
你叫什麼名字？
Chandler.
錢德
Chandler?
錢德？
What an unusual name.
那個名字真是與眾不同
You must have had terribly fascinating parents.
你的父母一定很棒
Oh, they're a hoot.
喔，他們只會大喊大叫的
And who is your friend?
你的朋友叫什麼名字？
I'm Monica.
我是摩妮卡
-Monica. Where are you from? -New York.
-摩妮卡，你們從哪裡來的？ -紐約
I'm not very fond of New York. Queens, I like.
我不太喜歡紐約 但我喜歡皇后區
What is this...
這個亮晶晶的…
sparkling something, honey, huh?
東西是什麼？甜心
Actually, Monica and I are engaged.
事實上摩妮卡跟我訂婚了
Really?
真的嗎？
Congratulations.
恭喜你們
When's the big day?
你們什麼時候結婚？
In two weeks.
兩星期後
I see.
我知道了
Well, I wish you both a lifetime of happiness.
喔，我祝你們兩個永遠幸福
So, you're bald.
原來你是個禿頭
Wait, wait.
等一下
We'd love it if you could be there.
我們希望你能來參加我們的婚禮
Really?
真的嗎？
I know it would make me happy...
我知道那會讓我覺得很快樂…
ma'am.
夫人
Then I wouldn't miss it for the world.
我一定會去的
I'm getting all misty here.
我都熱淚盈眶了
You'd think I was having my legs waxed or something.
你們一定會以為 我剛剛用熱蠟除過腿毛
-You okay? -Yeah.
-你還好嗎？ -我很好
Thanks for making me do this.
謝謝你逼我這麼做
Before we go on with the show, I want to say to the bride and groom...
在繼續表演前，我要跟這對新人說…
how lucky they are to have found each other.
他們非常幸運能找到彼此
In every life a little rain must fall.
每個人的人生都會遇到雨天
Fortunately...
還好…
in my life...
在我的人生中…
When I was growing up, I played the one on the far left.
我小時候演過最左邊那個角色
Remind me to introduce you to someone.
提醒我介紹你給某人認識
-Who? -Fourth gear.
-誰？ -四檔
What does he want? I wasn't doing anything.
他想做什麼？我什麼都沒做
Maybe he saw your hands slip briefly from the 10 and 2:00 position.
或許他看到你的手 只會從十點的位置滑到兩點的位置
Maybe it's Sergeant Sagittarius coming back to flirt some more.
或許是射手座警官 折回來想泡你
It's a different guy.
不是剛剛那個警官
-Good evening, sir. -Do you know how fast you were going?
-晚安，警官 -你知道你的時速有多快嗎？
No, I don't, but it couldn't have been more than 60.
不，我不知道 但應該沒有超過六十里
You're right. It was 37.
你說的對，只有三十七里
You're not ticketing me for driving too slow, are you?
你該不會因為我開得太慢 要開我罰單吧？
That's right.
沒錯
You know, officer...
你知道的，警官…
I had the weirdest dream last night.
昨晚我做了一個非常奇怪的夢
Oh, my God!
喔，我的天啊！
Your license, please.
麻煩你把駕照拿出來
You don't want to hear about my dream...
你不想聽聽我做了什麼夢…
Officer...
警官…
Pretty?
英俊警官
It's Petty.
是佩堤警官才對
I'll be right back with your ticket.
我馬上幫你開罰單
-You have a son. -I know. I know.
-你有個兒子 -我知道
-Feel better? -Yeah. Much.
-你覺得好一點了嗎？ -對，我好多了
Listen...
聽著…
Not that I'm insecure about my manhood or anything, but...
我並不是擔心我的男子氣概…
I need to hook up with a woman right now.
但我想我應該馬上去泡個女人
I understand.
我瞭解
You look familiar. Do I know you?
你看起來好眼熟，我認識你嗎？
I don't think so.
應該不認識
Maybe it's because I'm on television.
或許那是因為我是電視演員
-I'm an actor on Days of our Lives. -Wow. Really?
-我演出《我們的日子》 -哇，真的嗎？
-$4.50, please. -Oh, let me get this.
-一共是四塊半，謝謝 -喔，讓我來吧
These are for you.
這是送你的